Why have you held
my two men
for a week?
They resisted arrest
during the raid.
They were only visiting.
Kobayashi and Murase must be
released today.
Things have changed.
These raids are only
the beginning.
Ishida-san.
You are one of the few
honorable ones.
I do not wish to see you
end in prison.
This is a different world now.
It is time...
To shut down Chihara-kai.
You misunderstand
your own country.
Society runs smoothly because,
underneath it,
we hold back the chaos.
There is no Japan
without yakuza.
This was your warning.
Last week, the cops busted
the Hishinuma-kai.
Now last night, they took down
the Jinmon-kai.
And we have no idea how they're
making these arrests stick.
The police are refusing to say
what they're charging them with.
So everyone double-down
on your contacts.
Yes, sir.
Adelstein. Whatever else you've
been working on, this takes precedence.
- Go!
- Yes, sir.
You are still so bad at this!
You got a lot better.
I got good years ago.
If you'd been around,
I would have kicked your ass.
I win.
The girls on your campus are
good-looking. Having any luck?
You could say that.
Look at you.
Where'd you meet her?
Hayama-san took me out.
Last week. Kabukicho.
Kaito. Stay away from that guy.
He's not who you think he is.
Stop playing.
You think what he and I do
is some game?
Do not get involved with him.
- You hear me?
- You don't tell me what do.
- What?
- I'm not a kid anymore.
- Wait, where are you going?
- Leave me alone!
- Katagiri-san.
- Oh, Jake.
This is my new boss, Deputy
Superintendent Shoko Nagata.
Nagata-san, this is
Jake Adelstein. From the Meicho.
Very nice to meet you.
I was hoping if you have a second to talk
about these yakuza raids.
- You are covering yakuza again?
- For this story, yeah, we all are.
Unfortunately, I can say nothing
at this time.
I understand.
Off the record, could you just tell me
what they're charging them with?
Detective Katagiri
is unavailable to the press.
Have a nice day.
The police have made it clear
that the goal of this
new task force...
Is to eradicate us.
In two weeks, two of us
are already gone.
Get me the names
of the officers.
- I'll take care of them tonight.
- Are you a fool?
You want to throw more gasoline
on this fire?
Then what do you think
we should do?
My friends. We must stay united.
Fighting each other only makes
us vulnerable.
Wise words.
As you say, fighting each other
makes us vulnerable.
And vulnerable we can never
afford to be.
So, you have returned, Tozawa.
I have, Ichikawa.
Refreshed and re-committed
to our cause.
But...
Troubled by one thing.
Why has Chihara-kai been allowed to steal
my territory while I was gone?
So that's how it is.
More important things are
at stake now than territory.
This is not about territory.
It is about honor.
And honor demands
you must choose.
Are you with him,
or are you with me?
Gentlemen. With your leave, I'd like
a moment with him in private.
Long way down.
Are you thinking
of throwing me over?
It would not solve our problems.
So now our problems are mutual?
Yes.
I believe they outweigh
any petty grievances.
You call my grievances "petty"?
When last I saw you,
you made me beg.
You made me get on my knees.
Do you not remember why?
You sent men to my home
to kill me.
And yet...
I have found a way
to set aside my grudge.
Perhaps that's the difference
between us, Ishida.
I don't give up so easily.
You look tired.
Perhaps you need a vacation.
It did wonders for me.
Tozawa.
You light this fire,
you're the one who will burn.
I spoke to everyone
at the A/V Department
about the fire that burned up
the videotape.
It's clear none of them
was responsible for the fire.
Then the fire was caused by
faulty wiring.
Do you really believe that?
It's a lot more likely than what
you're proposing.
I agree. But what I am proposing
is possible. Is it not?
Maybe.
But we tell no one about this.
I'll ask the paper
to investigate. Discreetly.
I'm happy to help.
- No. You have work to do.
- But I...
Thank you for letting me know about this.
I'll take it from here.
The plans you are looking for
will look like this.
The name of the train station
will be here.
He told Claudine he always keeps
them in his home office
to ensure the location
stays secret.
Well, then it's a good thing
he invited me to his house.
He's cooking me dinner.
Samantha.
If you make a deal with Oyabun,
you must deliver.
- If you fail, I'm not sure if I can help.
- Like you're helping me now?
Is your mother here?
Thanks for picking me up.
I'll just be a minute.
Carry on.
I'm wounded!
Daddy had these.
I like them.
Thank you.
The babysitter is here.
You can't sit up. I killed you!
Yes, but sometimes the dead return.
Like on O-bon.
Will you return to play with me?
I'm sure he will, Daichi.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
Hey, it's me again.
I'm really sorry
about the other night.
Can you call me back?
Find anything?
I don't see any laws in here
that allow the cops
to arrest and detain yakuza
like this.
But somehow they're doing it.
What does your source
at the police department say?
He's not talking.
I'm trying to get Hishinuma's
lawyer to meet with me
at his office, but he's tricky.
So, is it the girl
from the embassy party?
That voicemail you just left.
I'm guessing it's the girl.
- You're not a bad reporter, are you?
- I try. So...
- Yeah, it's her.
- She's beautiful.
Tin-Tin is sure he's seen her
somewhere, but can't place her.
Well...
I'm pretty sure
it's over anyway, so...
Is there any Japanese context
in which not returning my calls
means anything besides
"Go fuck yourself"?
No.
See you tomorrow.
So, are you really in the FBI?
I would love to say
"yes" to impress you,
but no. I'm with the
State Department.
But your boss is FBI?
- Lynn?
- Yeah.
Yes, but I work with her,
but not under her.
I'm just a paper-pusher.
Facilitate briefings, that kinda thing.
I can think of worse jobs.
I'm not complaining.
I would've taken any post
to get outta the U.S.
So, now that you know, does that make
you more or less interested in this drink?
About the same level
of interest.
Is there somewhere more fun
we can go to?
Reminds me of a place
I used to go to in Bethesda.
- You're not impressed?
- I'm very impressed.
And grateful to you
for bringing me.
- Haven't seen you in a while.
- Yeah, busy. You know.
Are you as good at hitting
a baseball as this one?
Apologies.
My Japanese is not sweet.
He means rusty. He's American.
- American. Welcome.
- Thank you.
Jason Aoki. American Embassy.
What do you do?
Lots of things.
Nice to meet you.
Something I said?
We don't discuss
personal matters here.
Work at work, home at home,
bar at bar.
That doesn't bother you?
Dividing yourself up
into pieces like that?
Some pieces fit in some places,
some fit in others.
It's just...
I've done the closet.
It almost killed me.
I want to live my life, all my life,
in the open. You know?
I thought he was sick and dying.
That is what Tozawa
wanted me to think.
He had his men lure us into
taking back Kabukicho.
To turn the other gumis against us.
Then destroy us.
So we strike first.
So you counseled before.
Didn't you, Hayama?
And look where we are now.
What are we going to do?
Sato. You once spoke
of our need for guns.
I chastised you.
I was wrong.
Oyabun, I can find us weapons.
Not necessary.
I have made arrangements.
You will both board a train tomorrow
and meet a man named Ota,
in Nagano.
He's a former member
of Chihara-kai.
You will collect guns from him.
Ota was banished from our
organization for his behavior.
But he remains loyal.
- Sato.
- Yes.
Give him this money.
Then return swiftly
with what he has.
Understood.
Thank you.
Ma, I told Jess weeks ago.
I got the plane ticket.
Yeah, Joshua,
there's a world of difference
between having a plane ticket
and getting on a plane.
Fair enough.
This party, this whole thing,
is only gonna matter
to him if you are there.
Mom, I'm waiting for a call
from a lawyer who could be a source,
so I have to go, okay?
I'm sorry.
- Just tell me that you're coming, please.
- I'm coming. I promise. Bye.
- Jake Adelstein.
- It's me.
We need to meet.
Our usual place.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Erika, you are so good.
You had those guys eating out
of your hands.
It's less about how good you look
and more about how well you listen.
Oh, such wisdom from the Buddha.
So, what's up with you and Sato?
What?
Oh, you thought you could hide
that from us?
We are just
getting to know each other.
Oh, well.
That's what Samantha said,
and we all know
how that turned out.
Stop!
Don't make her feel bad.
Samantha is so over him now.
She won't even look at him.
It's true.
She's totally over him.
Wait.
Samantha and Sato
were together?
Honey, you have some things
to sort out.
What?
Next up is "Rosamunde"
by Franz Schubert.
I'm so glad you came.
I'm so sorry about the other night.
Just listen.
We don't have much time.
He's back.
Are... are you okay?
- Did he say where he went?
- No.
But when he left,
he was very ill.
Now, he's fine.
Like a new man.
New like what?
What does that mean?
Jake, you must stay
away from him.
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm done with all that.
- Promise me.
I promise.
I am not going back
to my old life.
I will see you soon.
What is it? It's late.
He's back. Tozawa.
How do you know?
A reliable source
with first-hand knowledge.
Who also said that he was ill
when he left
and now he's healthy.
"Like a new man."
- Jake.
- Yes, I know.
I'm not going anywhere near him,
but did you know that he was ill?
And where was he?
Until we know that,
we wait.
Remember, Jake,
patience is not weakness.
Understood.
Excuse me.
- Hey.
- Yes, sir.
- Two Asahi.
- Of course.
- Keep the change.
- Thank you very much.
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
You gotta relax.
Stress is bad for the body.
You could learn a thing from
your brother. That kid?
He knows how to relax.
He mentioned your... kindness.
But I would appreciate it if you didn't
take him away from his studies.
Now you sound like your mother.
Kaito told me all about her.
What a piece of work.
Dead dad. Fucked up mom.
I'd have gotten
out of there too.
My brother is all my mother has.
Kashira.
Please let him go.
I will be in your debt.
Tell your mother,
I'll take care of him.
You know how I feel about Baku.
But he lives for the Meicho.
I don't see him destroying
evidence about a key story.
Thank you.
I would have said that too.
But the way he reacted...
Telling me not to look into it.
Knowing you, you already are.
This is good.
Your brother still doing well?
Yes. For now.
Maybe his new medicine is really
making a difference.
I've seen it go well before.
Then it swings the other way.
And what happens?
He can be paranoid. Angry.
- Violent?
- Not to me.
To himself...
- Mostly.
- Mostly?
There were some difficulties
with our parents.
I used to have nightmares
about losing him.
Watching him vanish
into a crowd or...
In one of them he had climbed up
onto a roof...
And he looked me in the eyes
and then he jumped.
I live in fear for him.
But I've never once
been afraid of him.
Emi.
Can't I help you with this?
I don't need help.
And maybe this time the medicine
is working.
Okay, I have everything.
I have everything, okay.
Don't forget to keep an eye
on Kenji.
Samantha. I know how to do this.
Sorry. And thank you.
So, it's not a dohan?
- No.
- Do you like him?
Masa? I do.
But that isn't what this is.
It's for us. For the club.
Mixing work and love
never goes well.
Believe me, I know that.
Why didn't you ever
tell me about you and Sato?
Should I have?
- Wait, are you guys, like...
- No.
I mean, not yet. But...
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I should have.
I just...
I'm not sure I can be
with another yakuza.
If you do, be clear about what
you want from him.
And be careful with your heart.
Look who's the wise
mama-san now.
Okay.
Guess I'd better go.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Have fun.
Thank you for seeing me,
Sawada-sensei.
It's important
our readers hear
your clients' side
of the story.
Indeed it is. Because the police's
actions are outrageous.
Hishinuma-san and his associates
have had their bail denied.
I see.
That's very uncommon.
It's unprecedented.
The police have charged my clients
with Obstruction of Police Duty.
But that law is only used for
political agitators.
Exactly. Until now.
Adelstein-san, please let your
readers know about this.
Absolutely. Thank you.
Tell Maruyama-san I know
how the police
are detaining all these yakuza.
And what they're charging
them with.
I'll contact you once all of
the documents are in order.
Until then.
I will also contact you, ma'am.
Taxi!
Follow that Mercedes, please.
It's freezing, isn't it?
It's been a long time since
I've seen your ugly face.
That's my line.
Last time I saw you, you were
passed out on the floor of a bar.
Who's this little flower?
I'm Sato.
"Satou" like sugar?
Good thing I've got
a sweet tooth.
Not so fast.
Where are the goods?
We have to go to my house.
We'll take my truck.
You're driving, "Sugar."
Why didn't you say you knew him?
There you go with that stress again.
Pain in the ass.
- Here we are.
- Okay.
- Okay? Okay.
- Yeah.
Follow me.
- Just here.
- Yeah.
This is beautiful.
I'm so glad you came.
I want the tour.
I thought you'd never ask.
- This way.
- Okay.
After you.
- Excuse me.
- Welcome.
Kitchen is there.
And whenever you need it,
the bathroom
is around the corner.
Bedroom's upstairs?
I'm sure that view's amazing.
It is.
Unfortunately,
I spend most of my time in here.
- No view of the ocean.
- Actually, there is a view.
Hey Sugar, keys.
How're you gonna find a wife out
in the middle of nowhere?
Who needs a wife?
When I get lonely I grab a bear,
and put it on all fours.
- So where are they?
- No guns today. Guns tomorrow.
Your supplier's a day late, huh?
He's better with guns
than schedules.
- Wanna drink?
- Yes.
The deal was we get the guns
tonight. Not tomorrow.
You got a problem?
Oyabun didn't say anything about staying
the night with this guy. I'm calling him.
Good luck.
Reception here is shit.
Kanpai.
Sato, we could use
some firewood.
This is one of my favorite songs
from my time in London.
- Are you a good dancer?
- I'm pretty bad.
- Can I use your bathroom?
- Was I that bad?
- Of course. I'll finish cooking.
- Okay.
Fuck!
- You scared me.
- No. You scared me.
- What happened?
- My knife skills need work.
Do you have band-aids?
Let's grab band-aids.
- I think so.
- You all right?
I'm fine.
- Yes.
- Looks bad.
Makoto, did you use
all my sugar again?
Mother, the cake required it.
What kind of a son bakes cakes?
- Hello?
- Tin-Tin. It's me.
I need you to look up
this address for me.
Minato-ku, Higashigawa 7-5-2.
And tell me
what this building is.
I'm fine, Jake-san.
Thank you for asking.
I couldn't get through to anyone
at the office. I'm not near a computer.
- Tozawa's back.
- Tozawa is back?
Yes, I went to the Bengoshi-kaikan
to interview this yakuza lawyer,
and I saw him.
So, I followed him.
And now, he's in this building.
Minato-ku, Higashigawa 7-5-2.
Okay, okay.
I'll call you right back.
- Jake. Be careful.
- Thank you.
This is Jake Adelstein.
I need the immediate
use of a company car.
What?
Just... your new medicine.
I know, right?
This one is working.
Do you think Mom and Dad went
back to Korea because of me?
After I hit Mom, I know they
were afraid of me.
Are you afraid of me?
No. Not at all.
Sometimes I think you must
hate me.
Why would you ever think that?
You were in college in Chicago.
You had a whole life there.
And then you had to come back,
for me.
I would never hate you.
Will I ever meet your boyfriend?
What?
- Are you ashamed of me?
- No!
It just... I worried...
Maybe it wouldn't be
good for you.
Is he good for you?
- Very much so.
- Oh, yeah?
Dad isn't here, so it's my job
to look out for you.
I should meet him.
Follow that car.
- Where'd you learn to cook like that?
- In London.
I studied architecture there
many years ago.
I was so homesick,
so I started cooking for myself
to make home feel closer.
- That's nice.
- Are you ever homesick?
No.
Where are you from,
that you don't miss it?
- Utah.
- Utah?
Yeah.
I wanted more from my life.
I wanted more
from my life too.
- So, do you have anyone?
- You mean, like wife and kids?
Yeah.
Now would be
the time to tell me.
No.
It's just me.
- And my work.
- Yeah?
Me too.
- If you could wait right here.
- My shift is over. I have to go.
Just wait a minute. Please.
Are you kidding me?
Fuck!
I'm here to give
an English lesson.
Your client's name?
I can't remember.
He's a new client.
- Please, I'm running late.
- No appointment, no entry.
Yes, sir.
You really think you can do it?
Don't look down on me.
Just watch.
Try it then.
Show me.
Shut up.
I'm going to show you.
Told you.
Your eyes are going, old man.
This from a guy who can't hold
his dick steady when he pisses.
Are you jealous, Grandpa?
That my dick still works?
What about yours?
Excuse me?
I bet yours is a delicate little
butterfly-knife.
For delicate little butterflies.
How's this?
He is such an idiot.
Games are no fun unless
everybody's playing.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Your turn, Sugar.
What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
- Don't move.
Ah-ah. That's how you lose
a finger.
Sorry, my eyes are going!
You motherfucker!
Respect your elders!
You know who you're
fucking with?
Die you old windbag!
I'll kill you!
Kashira!
Fucking die!
Bleed out, fucker!
Kashira!
Please calm down!
Fuck this hurts!
I'm sorry that you have to drive me
all the way home.
I'm not. I'll take all the time
with you that I can get.
Oh, my car keys.
Be right back.
- Samantha?
- Yeah?
Did you go through my bag?
What?
What were you looking for,
Samantha?
Do you know how much
you've fucked us?
We can't take him to a hospital!
You are right.
Wipe everything down for prints.
Just kidding.
Out of the way.
Wait, wait!
- You could've warned me!
- Let's go.
- We need the keys!
- Go get them.
I allowed you time off
from your duties.
But you were away so long.
I have to come from Kansai
to handle matters.
For which I will always be
grateful, Nakahara-kaicho.
But now we must discuss
the future.
Your ways are old-fashioned.
From now on,
I will lead the organization.
So you must step aside.
You are a street punk
lucky enough to marry into
a powerful family.
Know your place. Or there will
be no future for you here.
Then you have made your choice.
Take this piece of trash out.
Do as I say!
Respectfully, Chairman,
please come with us.
Your men are mine now.
I am the Kaicho.
Word will get out.
I'm counting on it.
Oh, fuck. Fuck!